Well, one thing I've learned over the
years is that you can't be afraid of
failing. In fact, on my show, when I
help businesses, I fail all the time.
I'm normally shy to show those moments,
but tonight I'm going to make an
exception. So, let's take a look now at
some of my greatest failures.
One of my least popular ideas was for a
completely germ-free hot dog stand. At
outdoor food carts, it's easy for germs
to transfer from money to your food. So
to completely eliminate this, I designed
a hands-free method to apply condiments
to the wiener. Also, there would be a
second employee whose only job is to
handle the money.
What do you do with the wallet?
We're doing a germfree experience, so
you don't handle your own money.
Oh, really?
But people were a bit annoyed with the
money handling part.
Can I have my own back?
And the hands-free onion dispenser
proved to be problematic as well. So you
have to up one up, one down. When it
hits the table, the onions will fall.
Drop it. Keep dropping it up and drop it
fast.
[Music]
Oh,
this is not going to work. It's not
going to work.
That's nothing to do with the
contraption. If you drop a hot dog, you
drop a hot dog. The public just wasn't
ready for the germfree hot dog
experience. So, I laid the concept to
rest. Next, I had an idea for a tearless
way to tell a child that their pet has
died. To be an upsell service for an
animal hospital, the concept was to make
a video of the pet while it's still
alive, telling the child it's in animal
heaven. Now, I hired the only voice
actor that responded to my Craigslist ad
to be the dog. But when we showed it to
the owner's child,
oh, it's me, Maddie. I'm in heaven now.
So sorry I died. I miss you so much.
I'm happy here. So, I'm not coming home.
I miss
my talk like that.
However, she does all the time.
Goodbye.
It's okay.
He hated his dog's voice. Another
flubbed idea. Next. We all hate paying
those pesky ATM fees that charge us up
to $3 for basically doing nothing. So, I
designed an ATM that cleans your card
during the transaction. So, you get
something for your money. No transaction
fee, just a card cleaning fee. But my
mistake was that the washing process
took almost 7 minutes and people who
were in a hurry got a little frustrated.
It still surprised me because the
machine was doing a thorough job, but
even after all that, people still didn't
think their cards were clean enough.
This was not clean.
That looks cleaner.
No, there's still dirt right there.
People just weren't as excited about it
as I had hoped. And lastly, my favorite
ideas don't just help with business,
they're good for the community as well.
So, I approached a bar with an
innovative way to stop drunks from
getting behind the wheel. The concept
was to have a street magician stationed
outside the bar performing a magic trick
that allows him to secretly test the
blood alcohol levels of patrons as they
leave. And with my background in magic,
I offered to test it out. For my final
trick, I'm going to need your keys.
My keys?
Yes.
Great. Give the wand a blow.
Okay. A little bit harder. Right into
the top.
Okay. and you were over the legal limit,
blood alcohol. So, your keys are gone
and I cannot give them back to you.
Okay,
sorry. But that's when I realized the
flaw in my idea. If I held on to his
keys and he took a cab, the guy couldn't
get into his apartment.
Could I get my keys, please?
I can't because you're drunk.
Please give me my keys.
And the only solution at that point was
to drive him home.
You live far.
I know I do. Also, once I got him home,
I realized I couldn't just give him his
keys until he was asleep, or else he
might go out and drive again.
You need to see me sleepy.
I need to see you fall asleep before I
leave your keys, or else you might take
them and go out again.
Do you don't brush your teeth before
bed?
Usually not. I usually brush my teeth in
the morning.
Really?
Yep. I know it's kind of gross, but
nobody else is really paying attention
to the way my breath smells.
So, I had to put him to bed and make
sure he went to sleep. And if that
looking glass gets broke, mama's going
to get you a billy goat. Before I left
his keys.
So, as you can see, even the greatest
minds fail sometimes.